Nathaniel Milkosky

Software Engineer - Networked Products Division

Lawrenceville, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Nathaniel-Milkosky/c0a353a1515f891f

To work for an organization that allows me to apply my skills in computer science, that challenges me to learn new concepts and ideas, and that allows me to advance in my career.

Core Competencies And Skills

- Functional Programming
- Object-Oriented Programming
- Solution Design
- Communication
- Leadership
- Interface Design
- · Up to date with technology
- · Quick to adapt to new situations and learn

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Networked Products Division - Newtown, PA - January 2016 to Present

Developed new functionality for network and bootloader software. Worked with embedded C in order to produce software for small devices. Wrote code review and software testing reports. Worked in a lab environment in direct contact with hardware in order to produce quality software. Collaborated with management as well as other software engineers in order to understand the codebase. Worked with Subversion for version control.

Consultant

Kinect Development - Princeton, NJ - September 2015 to December 2015

Developed a Kinect v2 tool in C# that records depth, visual, and GPS information about streets in JSON format.

Web Development and Maintenance (Consultant), Forked River NJ Summer 2011 - 2015

Information Technology (IT) Intern

Enterprise Architecture Office Educational Testing Service - Princeton, NJ - June 2013 to 2014

Collaborated with various members of different departments to trial telepresence solutions in a corporate environment. Worked with groups of varying technical knowledge of computers. Analyzed data and implemented an algorithm that would present the connections between technology services in a "social network" style graph.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science

The College of New Jersey 2012 to 2015

LINKS

https://github.com/nmilkosky

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills

Programming Languages: C, C++, C#, Objective C, Java, Python, Lua, Erlang, Clojure, Assembly, Visual Basic, PHP, HTML.

IDEs: Eclipse, QtCreator, JCreator, Visual Studio, Code::Blocks. Tools: Regular Expressions, Qt, Subversion, git, POSIX threading, Virtualization Tools, Microsoft Office Suite. Operating Systems: Windows, Linux, Solaris, Apple IOS and OSX.

Nathaniel J. Milkosky (732) [...] 1103 Roundtree Place nmilkosky@gmail.com Lawrenceville, NJ 08648 milkosn1@tcnj.edu